fadisk.com 2018-06-29

# privacy | Tech News : Fadisk.Com

**Overview**  
This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to modify or correct it. The policies set forth below are applicable to the online media properties and electronic newsletters (collectively referred to herein as “the Service”) which are owned and operated by Fadisk.Com.

**Privacy Mission**  
Fadisk.Com is a privacy conscious organization and we are strongly committed to your right to privacy. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information.

**Data Collection**  
Fadisk.Com collects personal information from users during registration, and in certain areas of the Service where visitors provide information together with content submissions, postings to online community discussion boards, suggestions, surveys, voting and opinion polling. Fadisk.Com uses this information for its internal objectives, including but not limited to editorial and feedback purposes. You may be able to access and view portions of the Service without providing personal information, but other areas may require registration for access.

Fadisk.Com may collect non-personal information, such as information obtained from other sources, or aggregated information that does not identify individual customers. We may also collect the domains and IP addresses of visitors to the Service, as well as information such as browser type and operating system that is generally transmitted by your browser.

**Use of Your Information**  
Information submitted at the time of registration or content submission may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Fadisk.Com. We may also collect and use information about how our users use the Service, including search terms entered, pages visited and documents viewed. This information is unique-number identifiable, and is used for purposes of enabling us to provide you with a personalized user experience. Aggregated forms of this data may also be used in order to help us understand areas for future research and to identify future features and functions to develop for the Service. This data may also be used by the Service to identify appropriate product offerings and subscription plans.

The Service and its partners may also use your information:

To respond to an inquiry or request for information;  
To thank you for contacting the Service;  
To welcome you to the Service and to its products and services;  
To explain new product offerings and features of our services;  
To notify you of special promotions;  
To attribute content you make available through the Service;  
To communicate with you regarding customer service related issues;  
For the purposes for which you provided the information; and  
To enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Service, including this privacy policy and our Terms of Service.  
Registration  
In order to use some features of the Service and to participate in interactive sessions, you will be asked to complete a registration form. During registration, you may be required to provide contact information for yourself and the company you represent — as well as business information about the company you represent. Fadisk.Com may use this contact information as a means of confirmation of your identity, position, or relationship to a particular enterprise or company. By using the Service, you agree to reveal only information that you are authorized to disclose and know to be true. During interactive sessions, we may also collect your opinions and preferences regarding certain products or services. We use this information to provide you with quality services as well as with offers that we think are relevant to you based on the preferences you share at registration or during interactive sessions. Please see the Information Sharing and Disclosure section below.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
Fadisk.Com may share certain aggregated demographic information with our sponsors regarding the users of the Service and responses we receive from you via interactive sessions. The aggregated information that we provide does not contain any personally identifiable information.

Fadisk.Com may provide authorized access to personal information to employees and others who assist us in providing the Service. In addition, Fadisk.Com may share personal information with companies that have been approved by Fadisk.Com so that they can provide you with information about goods and services we believe might interest you. You can opt out of such sharing by e-mail request or by modifying your registration information online.

If you have accessed the Service via the Web site of one of our partners, then any information that you provide is provided both to us and to the partner. The partner’s use of this information is governed by the partner’s privacy policy. You should contact these partners directly if you have any questions about their use of the information.

Fadisk.Com may disclose your personal information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

In the event Fadisk.Com is acquired by or merged with another company, we may transfer your information as part of the business transaction.

**Special Offers**  
As a registered user, and based upon the preferences you chose at registration, you will occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers and newsletters. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. As part of our services, we may contact you with offers, promotions and information on interactive sessions sponsored by identified third parties. All of the content related to such correspondence is provided by our sponsors, and Fadisk.Com disclaims any liability for such content. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in promotions. By participating in such promotions, you agree to provide these third parties with your personal information, and further agree that their use of the information is subject to those parties’ own privacy policies. In the event you submit your information in response to a contest or offer provided by Fadisk.Com in conjunction with one of our partners, that information is provided both to Fadisk.Com and the partner.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive that may contain information about you and your use of the Service. Fadisk.Com utilizes cookies to identify you and your access privileges when using the Service. We also may use cookies to enhance and track usage, and better understand how the Service is used. Cookies do not contain your personally identifiable information.

Users of the Service may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. These cookies are set by the advertisers and are subject to those advertisers’ policies. By using the Service, you expressly agree that the Fadisk.Com bears no liability whatsoever, for real or perceived privacy invasion, or usage tracking technologies used by third-party ad services which are utilized by various advertisers. You agree that Fadisk.Com has no control over content served by third-party ad services, and that any remedies must be sought solely against those services.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. The “Help” section of the toolbar on most browsers will describe how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. However, if you do not accept cookies from a domain owned by Fadisk.Com, it is possible that the Service will not function properly for you at all times.

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
Fadisk.Com may provide links to other Web sites for your convenience and information. Fadisk.Com is not responsible for the privacy procedures of these other sites. The entities that operate these sites are responsible for the content of their sites, any products or services they may offer through their sites, or any other use of their sites. Other Web sites may have their own privacy notices in place, which we recommend you review if you visit them as a result of your use of the Service.

**Security**  
Fadisk.Com maintains reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards to defend against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration or destruction of the personal information in our possession.

**International Usage**  
While we make considerable effort to honor the laws and wishes of all users, the Service is intended for users located in the United States of America and therefore may not recognize foreign laws. If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using the Service, you consent to this transfer.

**Privacy of Children**  
Fadisk.Com and the Services it provides are not directed to children under the age of 13. The Service operates in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, and we do not knowingly accept registration by, and will not intentionally collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age. In the event that we learn that we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database.

**How to Change User Information**  
You may update or correct information you previously provided to Fadisk.Com by accessing your user profile. If you have any questions or concerns about the Fadisk.Com privacy policy or would like the personally identifiable information that you have provided to Fadisk.Com removed from our files, please contact us.

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
If you are a California resident, you are entitled by law to request an Information Sharing Disclosure. If you provide notice to the address below, Fadisk.Com will provide you with a notice of your right to prevent sharing of your personal information as well as a cost-free means of doing so. To receive such a notice, submit a written request to our Reader Services Department, specifying that you seek your “California Customer Choice Notice.” Please allow thirty days for response.

**Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We may change or update portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. We suggest that you check this page periodically so you are aware of any policy changes or updates. We will indicate above the effective date of the update or change.
